Twenty-one days after he was born. It was a beautiful day, so I left the house and came to the park for the first time.
Do you want some kaho?
I want some.
What do you want?
Kaho, just a sausage.
Not this sausage.
It's curry buns.
Curry bun looks good.
Okay, let's go.
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You can write for anyone, Momochan.
To be honest, everyone writes
It's okay because it's easy for everyone to write
It's just rock-paper-scissors for fun.
Ew...
Yeah.
Yeah!
Yay!
I've been writing about the sun.
Then I can't wait to write it.
I can't wait.
I said I wanted to write, too.
Then I want to write.
I can't help it.
Goo first.
Thank you
It's good!
Sweet!
I spoiled it.
It was sweet for me too.
It's really hot.
Hot. Oh, man.
Oh, no.
It's not there.
Once upon a time, there was a fisherman named Urashima Riko who didn't know what he was thinking.
He had no energy and never caught any fish.
Once upon a time, in Nagoya, he was taken by a turtle he saved
And when he came to the Dragon's Palace
The beauty that cannot be seen
What's good for you today?
Hiyo!
Did you drop a ticket to the relaxation area of this Famien?
Or is it a ticket for the Summer Es?
Famien!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're an honest man.
Tenkun?
Ten, ten, ten, ten?
Well, well, thank you for saving my life back then.
Ha-ha!
No, I didn't mean to help you. When did I help you?
No, that's the one I used in the back. What are you bringing?
What's that? What's that? What's that?
Kabuto crab.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Are you guys ataki? !
Kayo, kayo, kayo, kayo, kayo!
We did it, Annunzie!
You guys too, that day
1990s
Red dance, blue sky
Bouquet is blue sky
The heart is a blue flower
I'll step over the road
I'll jump into you
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
next preview
Next trailer
My lips are dying.
It's going to be a crazy scene.
I liked the second one.
And then we'll have a new kind of communication.
Let's see... 2...
Like it or not like it, dislike it or like it.
I want to hear all of them.
I want to mess up the scene so bad that you can hear it all
Like it or hate it, hate it or love it
I'll say it out loud, and I'll say every single word.
And after that
I want the dancing assholes and the watching assholes
I want someone who's a little bit higher than the tension right now.
I want someone who wants to go high
I want two people.
Yes, two Takami
I want two dancing assholes and two watching assholes.
Let's say you want to go high.
Dancing douchebags and watching douchebags
Dumbass who dances, dumbass who sees.
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight...
I'm the adult of the world, and I'm the best.
Dumbass dancing, dumbass watching.
We're all gonna grow up
♪ Together we're all gonna grow up ♪All together!
Come every time!
Once for every, twice for everyone together!
One more street!
O-negai hoi! Everybody ho ho!
Meega-hoo! Meega-hoo!
Meega-hoo! Everybody hooey!
Masha-sashi-ccha! Mameshi-cha!
I'll close it right away.
It's closing. It's closing.
It's closing.
I'm aware.
I'm awake.
I'm up. I'm up.
I'm not awake.
I'm not.
Oh, my God!
I'm in a hurry at the opening.
Oh, I see.
It's space.
Space.
It's not space.
Yes, it is.
Great. I'm sitting down again.
Let's make it space. Okay, bye.
We've got a couple of damage stations today.
Let's sing Luther and the Pop Rancher.
And that's the singalong, right?
Since there is a singalong after to your place.
It's that weird movement.
You in this before you go in when you meet.
Please enter properly.
Decide alone.
One more, please.
Please.
Ponk.
Let's go.
Oh, I peeked.
Where are we?
Outer space!
Winler!
Eithin!
Mewca!
Ebbie Ching!
Fight!
Thank you for your hard work!
Welcome home
The hottest
You.
The second
Toughest
Finish
Settle down
Oh-see
turn, turn, turn, turn
kuru kuru kuru kuru
come on, come on, come on
jump and move
Let's go
Right, right, right Rotate to the foot
Rotate.
Three, two, I'll shoot back.
Three, two, one, go!
(Wherever you look, there's a star of love)
I'll fall in love with you
JR East E233 Series Train
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching.
Your wife will be here today.
Mirei!
Your wife is coming.
Mirei.
Yuichi will change.
Yuichi's.
Because of our performance.
This wife...
Yuichi really said that earlier...
I'm not sure if it was a good idea to let him get to her.
Let's do our best.
Everything is for Yuichi.
For Yuichi.
Where are we?
Yoshijima.
Yuichi Miya
Fight Yuichi!
She said Yuichi.
Where am I? Yuichi.
That was my peak.
Here comes the game.
Hi, Mom.
Mom, are you leaving? Yuichi.
Oh, you eat from this side?
It's so good!
It's so good.delicious
I wish I could have had one.
I'm glad we only had one of each.
Mmm.
Please.
Please... hello.
We don't do this kind of delicious food.
Mayama will eat it.
Don't worry
Eat, eat
Bitter melon is coming
Can I spin this?
Go around.
Everyone.
I can't tell if I'm in front of something.
Who's up?
Let's go.
Why?
Because it's the Seventh Avenue.
How could they all be in the same room?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It can't be!
You all know what I'm talking about.
We're not gonna be confused.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Eight.
One.
Uh...
Mayama is one.
I'm eight.
Two.
Eleven.
Aah!
Shut up!
You're the only ones who know about this anymore.
Let's do seat number one.
Let's do number one.
If it's a number, I think it should be a million.
One million is fine.
One to ten, right?
You have to say it in front of me.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Someone's cracking up.
Four.
Did you say four?
Two.
Five.
Eight.
Yes, then I can read.
Yes, I can read.
Which is the longest day of the year: spring, summer, fall, or winter?
Summer, winter.
If I say all of them, can't I say akee?
Spring.
Spring, summer, fall, winter, which is the longest day of the year?
Days?
It's not spring.
Wheater.
Winter.
I'll read it one more time.
Which is the longest day of the year: spring, summer, fall, winter?
Days.
Answer the number.
Winter?
Summer.
Autumn, fall.
Spring.
Summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer.
Long.
What do you mean?
Summer, summer, winter, which is the longest day of the year?
1 year?
Correct answer.
The choices are spring, summer, fall, and winter, the longest of the year.
Why do you say that?
Okay, let's go.
How much is the change if I have 300 yen and buy a 100 yen candy?
100 yen.
I don't have any.
What?
If you only had 100 yen to pay, why not?
Correct.
Oh.
I used 100 yen coins, so I don't have change.
Oh, so that's how it works.
Ah, I see.
Next question.
Here you go.
The first letter of the English alphabet is A. A is before B. Then what's the last letter?
It's different.
Oh.
No, it's not.No, it is not.
B.
Correct answer.
Alphabet.
Yeah, I know.
I thought it was Eastern Europe.
Alphabet.
Correct.
The alphabet...
What's your favorite name in the alphabet?
I know.
Where does the English language come from?
England.
You know, the Great Great Open North.
Ha-ha-ha.
Tighten it up.
Correct.
Ah, I see.
I see.
That's frustrating.
There's a car with a big canker sore.
What?
I'm sorry.
You can drink alcohol when you're 20. You can vote from the age of 18. At what age can you drive a car?
Sixteen.
Uh, zero.
Oh, zero.
Zero.
Ah, that's amazing.
Totally serious.
Ha-ha-ha.
I think I just need a little more time.
Thanks for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work. Okinawa Sales Office.
I took it into consideration today.
I learned a lot.
Thank you very much.
The morning chime has rung.
It's a new chime, white. Please give my best regards.
Wow, that's great. Thank you for your hard work.
Good work.
Cute.
If you want, we can take a picture together.
We're not here.
We're the only one who's not here.
Mr. Maiyama.
We're not here.
Just the five of us.
We're at the end of our time.
Let's go.
Cheese!
Yes, cheese.
There we go.
Thank you very much.
Let's go, volcano aku-san!
Okay, here we go.
Okay, cheese.
Cheese.
Okay, then.
Thank you very much.
Hi.
Humblebrake.
Thank you very much.
May I ask you to ping pong?
Yes, please.
Hey, don't do that. Write it down.
Uh, Nimby.
Ninju.
It's a carrot.
I'll never get it.
Eye, eye, eye, eye.
My eyes.
Eyes.
I don't understand.
I don't know.
Akiyaku!
It's okay. It's okay.
I don't know.
I don't know
I don't like that room.
I hate that room.
I'm washing the car, but I'm going to have to ask you to come upstairs.
He's home.
Good night.
Yes, it's Ukiyo.
Ukiyo.
You ever pretend to be one of these?
No, I don't.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Congratulations.Congratulations!
I was thought to be great because I wanted to go home from inside the school.
But when the principal told me that since I wanted to go home as a whole, I would definitely let them in.
I was so impressed by Hinata's reaction when he told me that he would definitely let me in.
I felt that I had one minute left in the game.
I think Hyuga also became stronger and changed a lot with the new group.
I knew that he would definitely convey his thoughts to them.
I was sure that something was going to happen.
This time, I had a lot of reflections from last time.
After the last Famien, I started to think
After the last Famien, I wanted to pull everyone together and make them go.
I wanted to pull them all together and say, "Let's go this way," or "Let's get ready to go this way," or something like that.
I have been trying to do that for about a year now.
I have been trying to keep that mindset since the last Famien.
I've been working on it for a long time.
I've been working on it for a long time, and sometimes I've gotten off on the wrong foot.
I've been working on it, and now I'm here.
This year's Famien is the culmination of a year of work.
This year's Famien is the culmination of a year of work, but only a little bit.
The unison corrections after the misaligned parts were done very loudly.
I would sing very loudly.
I sing "Ha-ha-ha" very loudly.
As long as we are in Ebichu, our spontaneous work and our individual work are connected to Ebichu in the end.
There are many things that I am allowed to do after being a member of Ebichu.
I think that no matter how much I say it is me, as long as the name "Ebichu Private Role" is included, all the work will come back to Ebichu at the end point.
So as long as I'm in EBICHU, I'm not really Ayaka Yasumoto, I'm more like Ayaka Yasumoto.
I don't know if it's like a new weapon for Ayaka Yasumoto as a member of EBICHU.
I think it's difficult.
I am doing what I am doing to improve myself.
But at the end of the day, from the outside, I feel like I'm a member of Ebichu.
I don't know.
I don't know which is which.
You're fast, aren't you?
It's early. But I understand.
They look alike. They already look alike.
When I say good evening, I get up and I don't know what's going on.
Maybe it's fine the way it is now.
I cut my hair. No one will notice.
I cut my hair and no one notices.
Sheki cut my hair.
I've been doing "Eat the Omedama!" and stuff like this with everyone all the time.
And the song "Eat the Omedama!" we've been playing as Shimero Hamamoto and Shimero Nisei.
Even in those places, we looked each other in the eye, watched each other's movements, watched each other's mouth movements, and everything else.
and the movements of their mouths.
I get the feeling that we know each other and sing together.
I think these songs are helping us to grow as a group.
So, after the spring tour with the six of us, I think we have become more powerful.
I think that after the spring tour with the six of us, we have become more powerful.
I feel that the spring tour allowed each one of us to express our own atmosphere or individuality one by one.
I think it really helped us to become more self-sufficient.
I think that the two-days of the tour are a great opportunity to show something completely different from each other.
It is my own guess that during the three days of the concert, everything will probably change.
But we are going to be able to respond to a lot of different things.
I am sure that everything will change during the 3 days of the big show.
I'm sure that everything will be different during the three days of the festival.
So even if we are told that we are going to do something different for 3 days, we are not in such a hurry.
So, we don't have to be in such a hurry to do something different for the three days.
I think it's fun to know what song is coming next.
I think it's fun to know what's coming next, but it's also fun to know what's coming next.
I hope we can make it into a kind of musical show that people can look at every day with a new feeling.
I hope we can make it into a concert or something like that.
It's a lot of calories, and it's a lot of work.
It's a lot of calories, and it's a lot of work for us.
It's a lot of calories and a lot of work for us, but I'm sure people are looking for that.
It's a lot of work, but after we get through it, the sense of accomplishment is amazing.
I like the feeling that we all did it together.
I like the feeling that we've all done it together.
Okay, do you want to use this?
Okay, I'll borrow a coloring pen.
I'll borrow a coloring pen.
Oh, but they're similar.
Good morning.
Mie-chan, it's Carrie.
Where's Mie-chan Carrie?
Good morning.
Yesterday, I woke up at 2:00.
I was making dough for the Insta, and when I woke up, it was 2:00 a.m.
Finally, I'll update it every day. I was going to do my best this year, but I couldn't.
I couldn't do it.
Shocker, Zekamar.
There's nothing you don't want to be.
A world of just the two of us
I want to eat a lot of udon too.
It's okay, I don't eat.
It's okay if you eat udon
I'm glad. I haven't eaten noodles lately.
I'll have some udon.
Then let's just eat the dregs.
Just beef offal.
This is beef?
It tastes a little like chicken.
And a fried egg.
Tomorrow? The day after tomorrow?
One more time!
One more time.
Day after tomorrow.
Jump!
This crush is called Majipla.This tweet is called "Majipla.
Street, it's like a bright red hill
Take me there, I want you
I'll be waiting for you between Chaos and Cosmos
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you!
I'm running low.
I'm having a moment where I think it's really done.
I don't know, there was a lot of stuff.
Less.
Is it okay if I say "less"?
I feel like I'm getting organized.
Inside me.
I'm feeling refreshed.
It's not that I don't have enough stuff.
But I don't think that's a bad thing.
I don't think that's a bad thing.
I wonder what kind of decorations I'm going to put up next time.
I'm looking forward to it.
Next time, I'll try to appeal that it's not the temperature.
I see.
Your forehead is narrow.
It's right here. My forehead.
Because my eyebrows are here.
I can see it because my eyebrows are here.
But...
It's similar. I know, I know.
It looks good.
It's like a natural key.
Because of the big eyes.
Vegetables.
It's beyond dimension.
It's like, you know, like, a characteristically vegetable.
Pajamas.
Little eyebrows.
Cute. Little face, little face.
I've been alone for a while.
Is that what you mean?
I go to Kyoto by myself.
Really?
I like traveling alone a lot.
I even go abroad by myself.
That's great.
I like being alone too.
It's easy.
Me too. I like it.
That's a big lie. You're no good without people.
I don't know, it's just... I mean, I've been neck-deep like this.
I've been hanging out with friends since this morning.
It's past noon and I just want to go home.
Even though we went to the dreamland together, I felt tired.
So, let's go in the afternoon next time.
I'll go in the afternoon next time. I'm sure she's tired.
For a moment, I think it's okay.
And then I'll come back at night.
What a pain in the ass.
It's easy to understand.
I get it.
Okay, okay.
Let's go from the evening to the evening.
Later in the evening.
Do you want to go through?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
What should we do?
Salad, please.
You're the teacher, right?
And...
This one's close.
Yes, ma'am.
I love cucumbers.
begala 4
There is
Oh, no.
I love it!
Subscribe to our channel for good проф
mikyakyatte?
Cute!
If you take good care of it...
If I grow it carefully...
Will it turn out to be a normal Mikyatka?
Like this.
So...
I want to
I want to grow it like this.
If I leave it a little longer, will it turn into a normal cabbage?
Mikabetsu is Mikabetsu?
I really don't know if the tour was long or short, it seems like it happened so fast.
I think I've been able to enjoy it more than before.
It's all organized, for better or for worse.
We need to break that up a little bit.
I feel like if we don't break it up a little bit, the original Ebichu style will fade away.
That's why I decided to do it this way.
I knew I could eat all the shaved ice I want at Famien!
It's only at Famien.
I have a really crazy idea.I've got a really crazy idea.
This is the first time I've ever had
Ki-ice is so free!
Even at festivals, it costs over 300 yen.
And it's for free!
Amazing!
Super high!
He's on a roll!
It's so round!
I knew it!
My taste is similar to yours.
It's like an illustration.
In what way?
Basically, I don't feel like I'm hearing anything coming out of my ears right now.
No?
I don't feel like it's coming from inside my ears.
It's like a snare or something.
It's all in the instrument.
I only hear it in my ears.
I hear my voice.
I can hear it, but...
It's like...
I feel like I'm hearing it right.
I don't know.
It's like it's coming up behind me.
It's like...
It's like it's missing.
The whole thing?
Only the instruments are audible.
Voices?
Voices, orchestra...
Even on one song.
I'm having such a hard time.
It's so hard.
I'm amazed that you're always working on it.
I think...
I'm the one who's...
You dance to all the Evijoule songs.
That's why.
I know all the patterns.
I don't know...
I don't know.
I was thinking about how to avoid similarities.
And as a result
I don't think there are any similarities.
But...
I don't know...
something
but
This song is really difficult
But because it's a difficult song
something
I was able to do the choreography
I was able to do it and put it in everyone's hands
I just...
When I saw that everyone was having a good time
I'm really happy for them.
It's been great.
Even before I joined, I wanted to change.
I had no choice.
I was like, "What am I going to do?
What should I do?
I thought, "What if someone says, "I can't dance like this?
I'm sorry.
I've been so busy.
I know.
I don't know... the song...
The theme of the song...
I'm having fun.
I've been so busy
Like a day is not fast enough.
Like 24 hours is not enough time.
It's a song, so the choreography is a bit...
I can't go with that theme.
The choreography has to fit the theme.
I thought I'd make it busy.
I tried to make it busy.
But then I couldn't remember the choreography.
I was sometimes asked to correct the formations, but I found out that it was so different that it was very hard to do.
I learned how hard it is to learn a new formation because it's so different.
Lou's wall.
And the sound.
This is my sound here.
Not too small.
Yeah.
If it's hidden, it's there.
Songs
Bop, Pop, Pop
With flap
Bpop girl
Bagual
buffalo swan of trouble Sc theme
Cool
Hatake is like this
Oshimen-no?
It's like a stampede!
Hey, Hatake, it's like this.
You say "stamen" like that...
Oshime... "Thrower.Oshi, the thrower.
Okay.
Mr. Aoki is going to run like this and then
the moment you hit it.
Hey, you know what I mean.
The one that's easier to do, respectively.
Here's the ballet.
The swing is too old school here.
The moment it comes in for a home run, I'll go one-handed and come over here.
Soft shoulders.
Then I say I hit it, and throw it like this.
"Aiiiiiii".
His shoulders are soft.
Tecchan does this quickly, one at a time.
Hatake is easy for anyone to imitate.
You can do it too, Kaho.
Can you do it?
Want to give it a try?
A little slanty.
Oh, I'm sorry.
⤴
I'm sorry.
But today, I didn't think that Okinawa was a live music club. First.
Today's the last live house, so it's the semi-final, so
I'm going to do my best for the last.
An all-star runner at a live house.
When you say "all-star," it inevitably turns into an all-star game, doesn't it? In my head .
It's like the Separa All-Star Game in baseball.
I lost to Valentin.
Homeland view.
Of course, I'd get tired if I played twice in a row.
But I was catching up with him because of his great tenacity in the lower half of his body at the end.
It was amazing.
When I said that, Riko said so much.
It was Riko.
Oh, I said it. That's good. It's good.
It's nice.
Your arms are wide.
I have narrow arms.
Nice. They look alike.
This is your second time, too.
But the second time is fun, you know?
I keep telling myself that.
Yeah, I know.
Second time is fun.
It's fun.
It's amazing. It's beautiful.
It's beautiful. Is it new?
I'm tired.
What's that? Family?
No, it's not.
Real normal family.
Not a shrimp family.
It was peaceful.
Harmonious. Children were there in the morning, too.
About two children.
They were running around.
The wife.
Are there still stairs?
Just this one.
Come here.
Yes, Riko.
Come here, Riko.
Riko, come here.
This way.
Yes, this way.
It's exhausting.
It's tiring. Stairs.
I hate stairs.
You don't like stairs?
You still have a lot of stairs left in your life.
What, the third floor?
Third floor? Oh, there's a fifth floor.
It's closer than you think.
It's close, isn't it?
It's cute.
Let's take more pictures.
I took one earlier.
Here you go. Cheese.
No! No!
No way!
Get out of the way!
Go! Wait!
Scary!
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Scary!
It may or may not work.
Maybe it works.
Cute.
Take a picture.
Of course.
Mochi no Ron no Suke
What?
Rico's been in a groove lately.
It's springtime.
Month-less illness?Amenorrhea?
I don't know what's wrong.
What is it?
I don't know what it is.
Amenorrhea makes me feel rather sluggish.
Change of mind
Change of heart
Red now?
I wonder if they're finally getting used to me.
But everyone says that
The way everyone's talking about me.
They're like, "What's wrong with you?
The way everyone's acting.
It's like the part of me that I've been showing to Irian is coming out.
I was showing it to Irian.
That's how I felt.
That's how Aika said she felt about Rico.
When I hear Aika talk about Rico...
I get that impression.
We had this connection.
I see.
I didn't know that either.
That's why I said heh.
heh heh heh heh
spinning, spinning, spinning, spinning, spinning
Click, click, click, click, click
Wow.
Jump five times.
One, two, three, four, five.
Six, seven, eight.
Nine. Ten.
Wow.
Whoa!
Forward, forward!
Go up!
OK!
I'm fine.
Ahhh...
Ah~
Oh!
Yes!
Ready!
kuru kuru kuru kuru kuru kuru!
kuru kuru kuru kuru kuru
Ah!
Jump! Ready!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
OK!
Here come the engines.
I'm tired.
One.
I'm nervous.
I'm just a little tan.
Well then.
Let's go for it.
Okay.
Just don't fall down.
Only don't get stuck in the green.
Yes.
Let's do our best.
Are you talking to me?
To everyone.
Don't be capricious.
I understand.
I guess it's day and night, but at night again...
I don't know.
The psylliums are so beautiful at night.
I always thought it would be great in the daytime, but it's always great in the nighttime.
The festival is held five times a year, from bright daytime to nighttime, and this year, for the first time, it was held in the daytime.
This year, for the first time, it was held in the daytime, and I was so happy that it was over in the light of day.
I was so happy that it was the first time this year that the festival was held in the daytime and ended in the light of day.
I don't know.
I felt happy when it was bright outside.
It was really a completely different two days.
It was really fun.
I'm really glad that I didn't cry because of my injury.
I am glad that I am strong.
We have decided to hold a 3-day concert, so I would like to continue to do what we can do together.
I would like to continue to do what we can do as a group of 6.
We have another period of time after the Pamiye.
I am really looking forward to seeing what we will be able to show at the big show.
I am also looking forward to seeing what we will be able to show at the PAMIE's big show.
I'm also looking forward to seeing what they will show at the big show at Pamier.
It was the back side.
You took pictures of this side, too.
Can I take a picture?
Let's do it.
You in the middle of the dance
Time to go, time to go, time to go, time to go.
I'll bring you a promo smile
Defeat the wimpy monster
Aim for the super sur everyone shines
Remember this placeRemember this place.
Calm down.
Chu-chu-chu.
squeak squeak
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm so sorry.
Yes, it's a great pity.
I'll sing the chorus.
Just that part?
What's the word?
The chorus?
The chorus.
Oh, and...
"Declare a state of emergency.
To be heard.
The one to deliver
A smile
In the spirit of knocking down
Aiming to make everyone
Kyu kyuu
I can't do it there
Later
Bye-bye.
Let's do this.
It's good.
We made it.
You were smiling so much.
It worked!
That's funny. It's cold.
It's cold.
I said "Jura", but you said "Juju".
It's not "jura".
What does "Jurai" mean?
January.
July.
Not yet.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hime-chan's turn
The title is
Tetsuya's Title
Tension is rising.
Tension is rising!
Thank you for watching!
I love you, I love you, I love you.
Oh, my God, I love you.
I love you so much, I love you so much.
Give me love and I'll never have anyone again
I want everything to change, and I want to throw it away.
I love you. I love you so much. I want to believe in you.
Now you're smiling.
Thank you for your time.
You like it?
You like that?
Come on, man.
You make sure you say it right.
You're invisible.
If you've been doing this for so long...
Just put it away.
Go on.
You're invisible.
Students of the Church of the End of the World.
Starting today, you must move on.
You can't.
I won't do it.
Hard to die.
Hard to die
So, come here. First of all, it's amazing from the front of the station.
You think that maybe Akita is more famous than Tokyo.
For a moment when you come to Akita, you feel like a superstar, and there are so many of you.
That kind of scene is hard to find, isn't it?
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye, right?
Bye-bye, please.
Good night, Mr. *Okun.
Come on, someone's got to go.
Someone.
My hair looks fine.
It's fine.
Do this, do this, do this.
Do this.
Do it this way once.
Thank you very much.
The B melody of the first number.
It's like a person who just keeps slouching.
I wish I could do it there.I wish I could do it there.
I wish I could do that.
I'll leave it to you.
I understand.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm so sorry.
It's totally fine.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
I look forward to working with you.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
I have some disturbing news.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
Se-no.
Ouch.
Sacrifice
of the Se
heat question
Jesus
man
three
four
Ended.
It's over.
Okay, Kaho, please.
Is anyone here?
Mr. Chairman! Mr. Chairman! Chairman of the board.
Yes, sir.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous too.
Mr. Chairman!
Enjoy Akita Bunko.
I'll be there.
Where are we?
Akita!
We are M2!
M2!
Why do you say "We are"?
We are!
I'll take this hand, yeah!
Let's go for Dora forever.
We'll do it. It's not here.
We don't have to do it.
Is this what you want?
Black midnight in the dark
Do you hear that? Ine? Someone said...
The future, the future, the weakest point.
My heart beats faster when I'm nervous
Give it to me, Pramode. Smile.
Make a face, Pramode!
Aim for the superstar who shines brightly on everyone
Dramatic
Dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic, dramatic
Sadness is a dream that lasts
Every day that passes through my mind
The more I laugh
The sun that becomes light
Thank you for watching
Who will pray for who will live for who will sing for who will sing for who will sing for who will sing for who will sing for who will sing for who will sing for who
Let's go halo halo halo halo let's go halo halo halo halo
I'll go on not knowing what I seek or what I love
Let's go halo halo halo halo let's go halo halo halo
You don't stand out when you talk like a hawk.
Come on, don't be like that.
Let's go. Let's do it.
Raise your teeth, raise your hands, don't put your hands up, raise your voice
Peace on your right, peace on your left, everybody say, "Ready, set, go!
Yay, yay, yay, yay
Imadeken Iyaniken Akita Yamada Fujiyama Tohokuyama Tohokuyama
All together, let's go! Guitar solo!
Thank you for your hard work.
I heard I cried from you
What kind of night is it for you
Hajimari ha kirakira
Kono Koi ha Seven Color
Feelings that won't stop
I'll tell you
Hajimari ha Kirakira
This Love is Seven Colors
I think there was an announcement on our lovely website.
Mirei Hoshina got injured during rehearsal.
She couldn't make it out today.
Let's have fun for Mirei today!
Let's all have fun together!
I'm Rinko Kayama, junior high school student in Asorita, drop number 12.
Yesterday was a lagry blur, so I'm going to be a bit of a vitta vitta vitta today.
I'd like to be Vita Vita Vita today.
I look forward to working with you today.
Congratulations!
You all love Mire-chan, don't you?
Mire-chan, you came here to see the six of us, right?
Yes, I did. Then, let's do it louder than usual!Yes, I am. Then let's do it louder than usual and always!
Next, Mire-chan!
Yes, Mire-chan! Are you enjoying yourselves, Makogare members?
Isn't everyone's voice a little small?
Tiny! Tiny!
You can still do it, right?
Yeah!
Can you enjoy it all the way through?
Thank you very much. Please keep it up until the end.
It's over already? So early. This year?
I wonder what happened?
I wonder what happened.
I really enjoyed each and every one of them.
I really enjoyed the B2 live show, but I don't know if I can play it as well as I can.
I didn't really find myself playing at all, but I was able to have a lot of fun.
I had a lot of fun at the live concerts.
So I'm really looking forward to next year because I couldn't make it.
I wonder.
I don't know.
I don't know. I'm looking forward to B2, for example.
I don't know, it's not a world tour, but something like that.
I wonder...I wonder...I wonder...I wonder.
I wonder.
I wonder what it is.
Oh, but I think it's one big thing.
I'm thinking to myself.
I know this is a little off topic, but...
But, uh...
I think it's a little bit off topic, but, um...
I think one of the big things I'm thinking about is, and this is a bit off topic, but, you know, the old, the single from years ago, you know, they used to make music videos for them.
I'd like to try to recreate it.
With the current members and their ages.
If Koho-chan and I join, we can make cute music videos like "Butterfly Feki" and "Haitateki".
I'd like to do cute music videos like Butterfly Feki, Haitateki, etc. with the members who have grown up in our 10th anniversary year.
That's what I'm thinking about.
If you were asked to write only three songs, how many songs would you say?
Three songs?
I don't know.
But I would like to play Hi-Ta-Ta-Tech.
What else do you have in mind?
What else do we have?
What do we have?
What else is there?
Wear it, it's beautiful!
I've been told I can make music videos that I haven't made before.
But there are songs that haven't been made into music videos, right?
Oh! Oh!
That's so hard! I wonder what it is.
It's hard! I wonder.
What is it?
It's your favorite song, isn't it?
I wonder what it is? I like cool songs.
I wonder what it is?
But lately AVTU's music videos are often shot outside.
I'd like to do another music video indoors with a cute set.
I wonder what it would be? I'm not sure about the song.
Thank you very much.
I'm hungry.
What's the first thing you're going to do when you get home?
First thing? I'll play with my cell phone.
It's not a cute thing to do. I want to eat motsu nabe.
My family came with me, and I felt a sense of togetherness during the three days.
It was a pity that Mire-chan got injured, or that the six of us couldn't make it to the last big show, but I don't know what to say about the live show.
But I felt like I was able to express my feelings in front of the audience at the live performance.
I felt like I was able to express my emotions in front of the audience.
I felt that I was able to show my emotions in front of the audience in the live performance.
I have many things to reflect on, but I think it turned out to be a good Christmas.
I felt that there was a lot of passion for this year's year-end 3-DAYS.
Each member's passion for this year's year-end 3-DAYS was stronger than usual.
I mean, their passion for this year-end 3-DAYS was even stronger than usual.
Especially, I could feel the passion from Mirei.
During the lessons, I felt that Mirei-chan was very passionate about the event, and she was very passionate about the details.
Mirei-chan was always in the forefront of telling us what we should do, even on the smallest details.
She would tell me what I should do, and she would make a lot of suggestions.
She made a lot of suggestions.
She would suggest things like, "This is too hard for me to do," or "What's the point of doing it this way?
I was able to discuss with her about the set list and whether it was worthwhile to do it this way.
I don't know if she was in charge of this kind of discussion, but she was.
He was the one who initiated the discussion.
I saw him making suggestions and so on.
I could feel that you really put a lot of effort into it.
It's a pity that Mirei wasn't there.
It was a pity that Mirei was not there, but I felt that her spirit was in Makuhari.
I don't know.
I think it was definitely the six of us who were standing there.
In terms of feelings.
I could feel so much.
We looked like five, but inside we were six.
I felt that the year was connected to us more than usual.
To be honest, I often wonder what the beginning of the year started with.
I forget about that kind of thing, so I thought it didn't matter.
I thought it was just something that happened in the moment.
But this time, I remembered my head and my hips and my head all year long, so I felt connected.
I feel connected to it, and I feel like I've done it for a year.I feel connected to them, and I feel like I have done a year of work.
It feels like a year has gone by in a blink of an eye.
I have been told by everyone that I have changed, and I hope that I have changed for the better.
I really hope that I have changed for the better.
I hope that I have changed for the better, and I also think that I have changed in many ways.
But there are parts of me that I think have changed as well, and I hope that it will change for the better as we celebrate our 10th anniversary.
I hope that I can bring all my strength to the 10th anniversary in that direction.
I have not said much to adults in the past, but I have said what I think.
I thought that I would not regret it if I said what I think.
In the pamphlet for this year's big performance, the principal said that he thought we had changed the most this year, but there was no specific mention of what had changed.
But it didn't say anything specific, so I wondered what had changed.
I wondered what had changed, but I thought that things must have changed.
I think it has changed for the better.
I don't think it has changed in a bad way.
I may have come to like the group Ebichu more. I think I may have come to like Ebichu more in the past year.
Ebichu has always been a group that has had a lot of turnover in numbers.
But now, because of my comment, the group is moving forward with 6 members.
So, I wanted to say that we don't need new members now.
That's right, but I wanted to do what we can do as the six of us.
It was like a closing speech at the end of a big show.
When Yamayama told me that the 10th anniversary would be with the six of us, I felt thankful.
I was thinking that we should try not to share with you any feelings other than the ones we receive directly on stage during our activities.
It has always been my policy not to share my personal feelings with you.
But I couldn't do it anymore. I think they were all over the place. I think it came out quite a bit. Even on stage.
So, in that sense, as we approached our 10th anniversary
I think it was very stimulating for me to have three days of emotionally moving live performances, and for three days at that.
I think it was a good stimulus for me.
Up until now, Ebichu has had many troubles and happenings, and we have been able to overcome them over and over again.
We overcame them many times and dealt with them.
I think we have learned a lot from them.
I think that these three days were a confirmation that we have learned a lot from these experiences.
We have been doing this for 10 years, 9 years now, and it has not been in vain.
It was two days when I reaffirmed that the 10 years of experience we have had were not in vain.
I feel that nothing has changed. In my opinion. Have we changed?
The number of people has changed. The number of people has changed. Have they changed?
I don't know. I've been here for a long time, so I don't know.
Nakajima has changed, hasn't he? That's true.
But I don't care about such trivial things.
I have always had the feeling that I should do what I have to do now, whether it's a college show or something else.
So I don't really understand the change.
You have been in Ebichu for a long time, haven't you?
I don't know. I think Ebichu is Yasumoto.
I think Ebiichu is Sena, and I think Ebiichu is
I think Ebichu is Kashiwagi.
I think Ebichu is Kobayashi.
I think Ebichu is Nakayama.
We are all ebichu, and we are all individuals.
But the most important thing for Ebichu is not us members, but the family.
Without the family, a live concert would not be possible.
It wouldn't be a live concert if there were only us.
So, we are not able to perform in front of everyone as EBICHU without our family.
So I think I will do that next year.
This year, for the first time, everyone said something like "Ebichu is a family.
Ebichu is a family.
I don't know.
Family is Ebichu.
I don't understand.
Family and Ebichuda.
I like that.
I got a message from Miyai-chan.
So we all replied with a voice message.
Just kidding.
I love you. I don't love you. I don't love you.
It's a blessing to be able to see that kind of nonsense.
I'm so happy to be able to see it.
Yay!
Shuwaku! Shuwah!
From the top of the ass.
Swish! Squish! Squeeze!
On the top of my ass.
Your fingers.
In your arms.
Squish! Squish! Squish!
Snap!
Squish! Shuffling! Squish!
My ass...
Hey, you!
Get out of my way!
Ha!
Ha! Ha!
Yes, well, I'll be checking the monitors, I'd like to do it with ale.
by H.
Beautiful, isn't it?
It's like singing
Don't laugh, just believe
Don't laugh, just keep believing
It's so frustrating.
Thanks for coming.
Surprised?
Yeah, I'm surprised.
It's nice to get out in front of the family, even if it's just for a minute.It's nice to be able to get out in front of the families, even if just a little bit.
I'm sure the family will be happy.
And since Mirei-chan has been wanting to be in front of the family for so long, being able to be in front of the family, even just a little bit, makes us happy as a member.
I'm happy for us as members and for the family.
The family will be happy too.
And Mie-chan, too.
It's frustrating that Mie can't perform.
It's frustrating for us, too.
I hope you don't have to work too hard.
But I want to do it with everyone.
I want to do it with all six of us.
I feel like I'm forcing you to do too much.
I'm trying to hold myself back, saying, "No, no, no, no, no.
I know, I know.
I can't wait to do it with everyone.
I didn't actually cook the yakisoba, but is that okay? Is that okay?
Does it matter that we have yakisoba? Is it okay?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
It's so tiny.
The sink is sticky.
If you wear it too hard, the contents will come out.
Let me introduce today's performers one by one.
Some of the costumes today will be their favorite costumes that they have been born in.
Let's start with the first one.
Ten years of EBICHU is the history of this man.
This year, as always, he will make a big jump with his small body.
Attendance number 3, Rika Mayama.
Finally, the microphone is coming.
Go for it, this is Mayama.
Yes, the song of the end of the war number, in the first part.
There were some lyrics about a vocaloid in the middle of a shrimp.
Now, in the past, a big explosion of emotion, full of human touch
Bringing life to the goal, Ayaka Yasumoto, end-of-war number 5
Let's all get excited!
Yay!
Here we go!
Since the beginning of our enrollment, we have always been revolutionizing the people.
In 2019, I will continue to travel around sparkling and make everyone in the family smile.
Attendance number 7, Mirei Hoshina.
It's been a while.
I'm so happy, I'm about to cry.
I will do my best. Please give me your best regards.
When I entered the school, I was a raw child of Ebichu. Such Omochi will soon be 20 years old.
Still, he is in a period of eternal growth. I wonder how far he will lead Ebichu this year.
We aim for the No.1 in Japan with the Swallows. Attendance number 10, Hirota Kashiwagi.
I will do my best. Japan's No.1.
With a unique cheer and a warm hush-hush ease
Over the ordinary person in the shrimp.
He is good at making funny faces and kememe faces.
Attendance number 11, Kaho Kabayashi.
Hi, everyone, I'm going to raise you up.
Question.
[Question] [Question]
Now, please give a word from Mirei, who was looking forward to meeting you all at today's event.
Are you crying?
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
Let it out.
It's been a while, everyone.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time since I've seen you all.
I got injured during a rehearsal for our Christmas concert last December.
I've been working on the end of the year events, the Christmas University Vigil, and...
I also had to take a break from the Ebinegi Live.
I am really happy to be able to stand in front of you like this.
I am very happy to be able to stand in front of you like this.
It is still a little difficult for me to sing and dance.
But as you can see, I look very energetic.
I am still a little bit difficult to sing and dance, but as you can see, I am very energetic and I talk with everyone in a normal way.
I'm just starting with the tasks that I can do every day.
But I'm really getting better at what I do.
I am encouraged every day when I see what I have done today, and when I receive warm comments from everyone.
I am really happy when I receive warm comments from everyone.
I get really happy when I receive warm comments from everyone, and it makes me want to get better and work even harder.
I was really nervous about meeting everyone for the first time in a long time.
I was really nervous.
I was really nervous before the show.
When I came out and saw the psyllium lights for the first time in a long time, I was so moved.
I'm going to do my best so that I can perform with everyone as soon as possible.
I'm going to start the spring tour from where I can.
My physical condition changes every day.
I can do it today, but I may not be able to do it tomorrow.
I will do my best from what I can do.
Today, I wanted to do something together with you all.
I wanted to do this together with you all, and I am happy to talk to you like this.
I wanted to do one song specially for today, so I thought I would participate.
I'd like to participate in this event.
I hope that everyone will be able to see me singing and dancing for the first time in a long time.
I would like to ask for your continued support.
There was some kind of place where you could see me up there.
I saw it in a place like a room.
I thought everyone was moving so well.
It was a lot of fun.
It was so much fun, and you know all the songs.
Of course, it's Ebichu!
It was the most fun live performance I've ever seen.
It's so important to know the songs!
Congratulations!
Thank you!Thank you.
I don't know, 2 minutes is different from 1 minute, it comes as a surprise, a great surprise.
You go to unexpected places.
What do you think? Hinata-san.
But that's the song.
Thank you.
Thank you for you.
Thank you for the rice.
OK.
Let's say thank you to you.
I'm sure Hiiri-chan is watching.
She's watching.
Oh, there she is!
There she is!
Hirei-chan!
Where?
There she is!
She's in the room.
It's true.
That's amazing.
What? She's gone.
Hirei-chan!
I'm going to sing this song now.
You're going to take my picture?
You look modern.
It's very modern.
Like an Insta-evidence on stage.
Okay, Mire-chan, you took my picture, so I'm going to sing.
Okay. Okay.
OK.
Then, please be as capacious as Mire-chan.
Okay, I'm Hinata Kashiwagi, and here's a big thank you to you.
The sky is not always blue.
My feelings are not always honest, but
I want to tell you now
Thank you to you
No matter what time of day, you make me smile
I can do my best because I have someone I care about
I'm trying to be strong, but the truth is that I'm a crybaby.
I know I'm a crybaby.
Look me straight in the eye
I hold them deep in my heart
I want to tell you how much I care about you.
Sei-chan, it's your family
No matter what song comes on, seeing everyone singing and dancing as hard as they can is so energizing.
It's so energizing to watch.
I feel like I'm crazy about it.
I feel like I got more energetic today.
I think I was more energetic in the second part.
Also, I think I was more energetic in the second part.
I thought that I liked the space.
I thought I liked the space.
I really liked the atmosphere of being absorbed in the dream.
In the evening darkness, hugging each other on the sofa.
When the lights are turned off, the window frames are flying away.
With you
When the dream wakes up
I touch your back and it's like today's sky
Cloudy and bottomless, like today's sky
You gave up your eyes, they can't see me.
I've been trying not to look at you for so long
xerasera spell I want to believe in that man, but
I want to believe in him, but my fingers are fraying together, my fingers are getting cold.
Hey, Kisela, Kisela, Kisela, Kisela, Kisela
Hey, Kisela, Kisela, Kisela, Kisela
I've been lying on my knees watching you.
Your favorite.
Pure, boring movies.
I thought I understood everything.
It was the sweetest place on earth.
Kesera sera, kesera sera, kesera sera
I want to believe in that man
But he gave it to me for the first time
Don't lock me up in your youth
I thought it was a kiss
I still have it in my pocket
I tried to spread the words
But I realized they were already fake
I threw them in the station trash
Kesera-senra no mahoutsura no mahoutsura no mahoutsura no mahoutsura
I want to believe in that man
but you don't see my reflection
Beyond the dullness of the sky
Hey, don't let me disappear
Alvida Shabada.
Your neck is working out a lot.
Yui, I'm working on my neck.
It's the next genus part. Part.
It's a Roman part. That's what it looks like.
We're going to the next interview, so come here.
Okay.
You scared me.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Stop it!
Soft-chan spilled.
I'm terrible.
It's okay. You look like a middle schooler.
It's like a middle of a shrimp.It looks like a shrimp.
Cute.
Good night.
Thanks for watching!
I spent a lot of time filming this scene called "Darugarami," but it was cut from the movie.
I have to accept the fact that this is a reality.
I'm having a hard time accepting the reality that they don't use it even though I'm having a lot of fun with it.
I'm not very good at it, am I?
There's a part of me that can't take it in.
But there is also the reality that I end up in this kind of open atmosphere.
I wish Mr. Nakayama would tell me that.
You are in Akita now, right?
I really want to eat misty tampo.
When I had it last year, it was so delicious in the moment I put it in my mouth.
I couldn't swallow it.
I was sad that if I swallowed it at this moment, I would never see it again.
But I know that misty dandelion is there to be swallowed
So, the reality is that I can't accept it if I don't swallow it.
That's why I've been trying so hard.
What happened?
It's over.
I'm not in a good mood today.
I can't even swallow our reality.
We're in the wrong mode.
I'm sure they're fine.
I'm getting a little tired of it.
If we get tired of it, then they won't use us anymore.
I can't take it.
I don't like talking about this all the time.
I don't know which way to swallow it.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, I'm just starting to get tired of saying this.
I'm getting... I'm getting... I'm getting... I'm getting...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Self-absorbed
It's frustrating, or it's hard to swallow...
Hang in there, Rika!
Hang in there!
Swallow it!
Go for it!
Swallow!
What is it with people who say "hang in there"?
I'm trying.
Are you trying?
I'm looking at you. I'm looking at you.
You don't have to.
I'm watching you.
Swallow.
Kashiwagi-san, may I speak?
He's talking.
Are you talking?
How are you going to end this?
The art is that Kashiwagi doesn't follow the groove.
It's a pity.
He's really following.
So, there is the art of being cut in the making of the film.
There's not many people who speak so hard.
He's really rooting for everyone.
Are you really rooting for me?
I'm rooting for you guys.
From the bottom of my heart.
When you bite into a hormone called yakiniku...
You put something called hormone in your mouth.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
That hormone...
Don't cry
Go for it!
I'm rooting for you, hormones!
Hormones are there every time you eat...
But I can't swallow it
Hang in there
Don't worry, you can swallow it
Hang in there.
But by baking them crispy and charred
I'm going to swallow it
It's the first time I've ever found myself able to swallow.
Good for you.
I'm sure you'll continue to hit walls of un-swallowable reality.
I'm going to have to keep knocking it down.
On that note...
When I eat my favorite white bean paste at a restaurant
I have a hard time swallowing it.
It's hard.
I end up taking it home with a rice cake in my mouth.
I'm like that.
This part of the school lunch
I can't swallow this part of the lunch.
It's too precious.
It's hard to eat suppo.
When I chew it, I can feel the tasty liquid coming out of the sappo.
It takes a lot of courage to get it out.
Snap!
So...
I don't know...I don't know.
I can't find the words.
Hang in there, Rika-chan. Calm down.
You know...
Like hormones.
Looks delicious.
Looks good?